Jeffrey Diaz (813) 389-0244 JeffreyDiaz813@gmail.com June 14<sup>th</sup> 2016

## To whom it may concern:

I would like to apply for a position in your facility. I am suited for the job because I am well trained in computer fields and have had great experiences on the job. I am very well organized and work well with others. Leading others to get a task done is something I find important and I can do with the best of my abilities. I have a great knack for time management and know how to use the time given to accomplish my work in a timely fashion. I have great communication skills and know how to put them into action. I am very patient and know how to handle difficult situations. I feel I can be a great asset to your team. If the chance is provided to me it would not be regrettable. I can be reached at (813) 389-0244 any time before 8AM or after 6:00PM. You can leave me a voice mail if you call between 8am and 4PM. Thank you and I look forward to hearing from you.

Sincerely,

Jeffrey Diaz

## **Experience:**

# United Health Care- June 2015- Current

#### **Title: Provider Customer Service**

- Reviewing Claims
- Provide benefit information according to members policy
- HIPPA
- Creating authorizations for surgical procedures
- · Creating service requests when claims have been processed incorrectly
- Going over payments on claims with providers
- Provide customer service and be courteous
- Multi-Task
- Fax request for acknowledgement/outcome letters on Claims Appeals
- Send claims back for reprocessing
- Learn CPT codes, HCPCS, Modifiers, Revenue Codes, Adjustment Codes,

 Letting providers know what third party handles their authorization depending if its Radiology, Physical Therapy, Chiropractic, Orthodontics.

# 3M: Electronic Monitoring [Security & Safety Division]

Title: Team Lead of Customer Service / Technical Support

July 2011-February 2015

- Trouble shooting GPS monitoring device with parole officers
- Finding resolution to unknown technical issues with devices upon occurrence
- Contacting offenders on Alarms or Violations
- Documenting everything the offender states on the phone call for court purposes
- Knowledge of all types of equipment RF, One piece, 2 piece, Alcohol Units
- Leadings agents to the correct Queue
- Monitoring device calls and making sure they are communicating with servers
- Creating trouble tickets with wireless network provider AT&T or T-Mobile
- Assigning Breaks and Lunch Schedule
- Assisting Agents in different call centers with trouble tickets or officer questions
- Responding to Emails in regards to hardware/software/server issues

# Mercantile Adjustment Bureau

Representing: M & I Bank

Title: Customer Service/Collector

March 2010-June 2011

Call Center/ Outbound & Inbound

- Skip Tracing
- Providing Extensions or Referring to Loss Mitigation
- Collecting on Over Drawn Accounts
- Working with Small Businesses
- Collecting on Past due Credit Cards

## **One Touch Direct**

Representing: T-Mobile

**Title:** Customer Service Representative

Aug 2009-March 2010

Call Center/Outbound & Inbound

- Providing customer service
- · Verifying customer info
- Trouble Shooting on cell phones

Making Changes to their phone plans

# Coleman & Associates Inc. Representing: Verizon Online

Title: Customer Service/billing/retention Rep

March 2008- June 2009 Call Center/Inbound

- Helping customers with their Bill
- · Applying Credits on accounts
- Saving customers that want to cancel
- Business Billing
- First Call Resolution

# **Uniform City**

Title: Customer Service Representative

Dec 2006-March 2008 Call Center/Inbound

- Placing orders for customers
- Up sell
- Track packages thru UPS & FEDEX
- Mail out magazines to customers
- · Check Availability of items at warehouse

## **Skills and Qualifications:**

- Computer Skills: Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, and Power Point)
- Working in a busy call center environment
- Excellent written & Verbal Communication
- Bilingual/Spanish
- Collecting/Mortgage collections/Auto Finance Collections/Commercial
- Up selling/Sales
- Knowledge of FDCPA
- Detailed oriented
- Ability to multi-task and work independently
- 10-key
- Technical Support/Troubleshooting/Data Entry
- 40WPM

#### **Education:**

Walter L. Sickles Tampa, FL High School Diploma June 2006

References are available upon request.